105 Dairy Rd. Melrose, FL 32666 | 352-235-1270

lkm@lkminor.com

## **Profile**

I am an easy going guy who likes to explore possibilities and find challenges. I am very detail oriented, like to rethink, redesign, rebuild anything keeping in mind that something can always be made better or more efficient. I have experience in a leadership role as well as working solo and in team environments. I am primarily a Developer with Sys-Ops training, Graphic Design, Database Management, Helpdesk support and Quality Management skills and experience.

# Core Qualifications

- Quality Control
- Content Management
- Problem Solving
- Collaborative skills
- Object Oriented Programming
- Development lifecycle management
- Project management

# Experience

#### WEB DEVELOPER

APRIL 2014 - PRESENT

### **GROUP INTERACTIVE NETWORKS – GAINESVILLE, FL**

Managing code releases from user issues to bug fixes and enhancements all the way from development to production releases. I run most of the companies quality control and unit testing. - IT, MySQL database manipulation, PHP development, Unit Testing, Quality control, AWS: Opsworks, EC2, RDS, S3, Cloudwatch, SQS, Elastic Beanstalk, Elasticache

#### **COMPUTER OPERATOR LVL. 2**

DEC 2013 - SEPT 2014

#### FLORIDA FISH & WILDLIFE CONSERVATION - GAINESVILLE, FL

Building in house scientific applications for use of the Florida Shorebird Database System. Using <u>ASP.NET</u> and Google API's. - ASP.NET, C#, MySQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript

## SALES ASSOCIATE MARCH 2011 - JULY 2011

### RADIOSHACK - KEYSTONE HEIGHTS, FL

Computer tech, sales, problem solving, troubleshooting, electrical advising, radio advising, tv/satellite advising.

## **COMPUTER TECH AND GRAPHIC DESIGN SPECIALIST**

JAN 2009 - JUNE 2010

## UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA CRANIOFACIAL CENTER - GAINESVILLE, FL

Build and maintain 3 websites, Maintain 2 patient databases of over 8,000 patients annually. Computer maintenance, updates, security, troubleshooting. Graphic design, design pamphlets, copyrighted images and video editing.

# Education

## Bachelor of Science, Web Design & Development

2013

Full Sail University - Winter Park, FL

# **Technical Skills:**

AWS: Opsworks, EC2, RDS, S3, Cloudwatch, SQS, Elastic Beanstalk, Elasticache, Chef

Server OS: Microsoft Server, Unix Server, Ubuntu/Redhat

Languages: Java, C#, node.js, jQuery, ASP, PHP, PHP Unit, MySQL, MongoDB, GIS